Finding Aid for Michigan State Land Office Board records, 1816-1924
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Plat Maps
  - Lower Peninsula
    - Wexford County 1837-1839, 1848, 1852
29W 66
30-31W 67
32W 68
33W 69
34-35W 70
36W 71
37-38W 72
39W 73
44N supplement 88
1-3E 77
1-3W 52
4-6W 53
7-8W 54
9-11W 55
12-13W 56
14-15W 57
16-17W 58
18-19W 59
20-21W 60
22-23W 61
24-25W 62
26W 63
27W 64
28W .65
29W 66
30-31W 67
32W 68
33W 69
34-35W 70
36W 71
37-38W 72
39-40W 73
41-42W 74
45N supplement 88
1-3E 77
1-3W 52
4-6W 53
7-8W 54
9-11W 55
12-13W 56
14-15W 57
16-17W 58
18-19W 59
20-21W 60
22-23W 61
24-25W 62
26W 63
27W 64
28W 65
29W 66
30-31W 67
32W 68
33W 69
34-35W 70
36W 71
37-38W 72
39-40W 73
41-43W 74
44-46W 75
46N 1-2E 77
1-3W 52
4-6W 53
7-8W 54
9-10W 55
11-13W 56
14-15W 57
16-17W 58
18-19W 59
20-21W 60
22-23W 61
24-25W 62
26W 63
27W 64
28W 65
29W 66
30-31W 67
32W 68
33W 69
34-35W 70
36W 71
37-38W 72
39-40W 73
41-43W 74
44-46W 75
47W 76
47N 1-2E 77
1-3W 52
4-6W 53
7-8W 54
9-10W 55
11-13W 56
14-15W 57
16-17W 58
18-19W 59
20-21W 60
22-23W 61
24-25W 62
26W 63
27W 64
28W 65
29W 66
30-31W 67
32W 68
33W 69
34W 70
35-36W 71
37-38W 72
39-40W 73
41-43W 74
44-46W 75
47-48W 76
48N 1-2E 77
5W 53
6-8W 54
9-10W 55
11-12W 56
13-15W 57
16-17W 58
18-19W 59
20-21W 60
22W 61
25W 62
26W 63
27W 64
28W 65
29W 66
30W 67
31-32W 68
33W 69
34W 70
35-36W 71
37-38W 72
39-40W 73
41-43W 74
44-46W 75
47-48W 76
49N no E none
5W 53
6-8W 54
9-10W 55
11-12W 56
13-15W 57
16W 58
25W 62
26W 63
27W 64
28W 65
29W 66
30W 67
31-32W 68
33W 69
34W. 70
35-36W 71
37-38W 72
39-40W 73
41-42W 74
43-46W 75
47-48W 76
50N (no E)
5W 53
6-8W 54
9W 55
11-12W 56
13W 57
26W 63
27W 64
28W 65
29W 66
30W 67
31-32W 68
33W 69
34W 70
35-36W 71
37W 72
38-40W 73
41-42W 74
43-46W 75
51N (no E)
5W 63
6W 54
26W 63
27W 64
28W 65
29W 66
30W 67
31-32W 68
33W 69
34W 70
35-36W 71
37W 72
38-39W 73
40-42W 74
43-44W 75
52N (no E)
27W 64
28W 65
29W 66
30W 67
31-32W 68
33W 69
34W 70
35-36W 71
37W 72
38-39W 73
40W 74
52N (no E)
53N (no E)
29W 66
30W 67
31W 68
32-33W 69
34W 70
35W 71
36-37W 72
38-39W 73
54N (no E)
31W 68
32-33W 69
34W 70
35W 71
36-37W 72
55N (no E)
31W 68
32-33W 69
34W 70
35W 71
36W 72
56N (no E) none
30W 67
31W 68
32-33W 69
34W 70
35W 71
57N (no E) none
29W 66
30W 67
31W 68
32-33W 69
58N (no E)
26W 63
27W 64
28-29W 66
30W 67
31W 68
32W 69
59N (no E) none
27W 64
28-29W 66
30W 67
63N (no E)
36-39W 76
64N (no E)
36-39W 76
65N (no E)
34-37W 76
66N (no E)
33-35W 76
67N (no E)
32-34W 76
1S 1-7E 80
8-13E 81
1-2W 82
3-4W 83
5-9W 84
10-13W 85
14-17W 86
2S 1-6E 80
7-12E 81
1-2W 82
3-4W 83
5-9W 84
10-13W 85
14-18W 86
3S 1E 78
2-6E 80
7-11E 81
1-2W 82
3-4W 83
5-9W 84
10-13W 85
14-18W 86
4s 1-6E 78
7-8E 79
9-10E 81
1-2W 82
3-4W 83
5-9W 84
10-13W 85
14-17W 86
18-19W 87
5S 1-6E 78
7-10E 79
1-2W 82
3-4W 83
5-8W 84
9-13W 85
14-17W 86
18-19W 87
6S 1-6E 78
7-10E 79
1-2W 82
3-4W 83
5-8W 84
9-13W 85
14-17W 86
18-20W 87
7S 1-6E 78
7-9E 79
1-2W 82
3-4W 83
5-8W 84
9-12W 85
13-17W 86
18-21W 87
8S 1-5E 78
6-9E 79
lW 82
2-4W 83
5-8W 84
9-12W 85
13-17W 86
18-22W 87
9S 1-5E 78
6-9E 79
lW 82
2-4W 83
10S 1-5E 78
6-9E 79
lW 82
2-4W 83